Guide to the Electronic Arts Sports Game Collection M2246
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Electronic Arts sports game collection
1992-2010
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Electronic Arts
M2246
8 Linear Feet: 16 boxes
Collection of sports video games produced by Electronic Arts.
Scope and Contents
Collection of sports-related video games produced by Electronic Arts. The games have been arranged by sport, including baseball, football, boxing, golf, and racing.
Biographical / Historical
Electronic Arts (EA) is a Silicon Valley-based video game company. Its headquarters are in Redwood City, California, though it was initially founded in San Mateo in 1982.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Games are not available for playing, but the media and accompanying materials may be examined for research purposes. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use.
Video games.; Electronic Arts
- Series 1. Baseball
  - Triple Play 97 (PC), 1996 (Box 1)
  - Triple Play 97 (PS1), 1996 (Box 1)
  - Triple Play 98, 1997 (Box 1)
  - MVP Baseball 2004 (Box 1)
  - MVP Baseball 2005 (Box 1)
- Series 2. Basketball
  - NBA Live 96, 1996 (Box 2)
  - NBA Live 98, 1997 (Box 2)
  - NCAA March Madness 2004, 2003 (Box 2)
  - NBA Live 07, 2006 (Box 2)
- Series 3. Boxing
  - Evander Holyfield's Real Deal Boxing, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Knockout Kings 2001, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Knockout Kings 2002 (PS2) (Box 3)
  - Knockout Kings 2002 (Xbox) (Box 3)
  - Fight Night 2004 (Box 3)
  - Fight Night Round 3 (PSP), 2006 (Box 3)
  - Fight Night Round 3 (Xbox 360), 2006 (Box 3)
- Series 4. Football
  - Madden NFL '94, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Bill Walsh College Football '95, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Madden NFL '95, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Madden NFL 2001, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Madden NFL 2002 (GameCube), 2001 (Box 4)
  - Madden NFL 2002 (PS2), 2001 (Box 4)
  - Madden NFL 2002 (Xbox), 2001 (Box 4)
  - NCAA Football 2002, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Madden NFL 2003, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Madden NFL 2004, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Madden NFL 2005 (DS), 2004 (Box 4)
  - Madden NFL 2005 (Xbox), 2004 (Box 4)
  - NCAA Football 2005, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Madden NFL 06 (PS2), 2005 (Box 5)
  - Madden NFL 06 (Xbox 360), 2005 (Box 5)
  - Madden NFL 07, 2006 (Box 5)
  - NCAA Football 07, 2006 (Box 5)
  - NCAA Football 08, 2007 (Box 5)
  - NCAA Football 09, 2008 (Box 5)
- Series 5. Golf
  - PGA Tour Golf II, 1992 (Box 6)
  - Golf (Virtual Boy), 1995 (Box 6)
  - PGA Tour Pro (Includes Pebble Beach Golf Links add-on disc), 1997 (Box 6)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2000, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2000 (PC) (Box 7)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2002 (PC) (Box 7)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2002 (PS2) (Box 7)
  - Sid Meier's SimGolf, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2003, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2004, 2003 (Box 7)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 2005, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour (PSP), 2005 (Box 7)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 06, 2005 (Box 7)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 07 (PS3), 2006 (Box 7)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 07 (Xbox 360), 2006 (Box 7)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 08 (PS3), 2007 (Box 8)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 08 (PSP), 2007 (Box 8)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 08 (Xbox 360), 2007 (Box 8)
  - Tiger Woods PGA Tour 11, 2010 (Box 8)
- Series 6. Hockey
  - NHL '94, 1993 (Box 9)
  - NHL 95, 1994 (Box 9)
  - NHL 96, 1995 (Box 9)
  - NHL 97, 1996 (Box 9)
  - NHL 98, 1997 (Box 10)
  - NHL 99, 1998 (Box 10)
  - NHL 2000, 1999 (Box 10)
  - NHL 2002, 2001 (Box 11)
- Series 7. Racing
  - Road & Track Presents: The Need for Speed, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Road & Track Presents: The Need for Speed Special Edition, 1996 (Box 12)
  - NASCAR Revolution, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Superbike World Championship, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Superbike 2000 (Box 13)
  - Motor City Online, 2001 (Box 13)
  - SSX 3, 2003 (Box 13)
- Series 8. Miscellaneous
  - Rugby World Cup 1995 (Box 16)
  - SimCity 3000, 1998 (Box 14)
  - Sim Theme Park, 1999 (Box 14)
  - SimCoaster, 2000 (Box 14)
  - The Sims: Livin' Large Expansion Pack, 2000 (Box 15)
  - The Sims: House Party Expansion Pack, 2001 (Box 15)
  - The Sims: Hot Date Expansion Pack, 2001 (Box 15)
  - The Sims Online, 2002 (Box 15)
  - Crysis, 2007 (Box 15)
  - Crysis, 2007 (Box 16)
  - Spore: Creature Creator, 2008 (Box 16)
  - Spore: Creature Creator, 2008 (Box 16)